《诉讼双雄》前情提要
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
戈登不是真的想掌权
Gordon doesn't want to take over.
他是想争取一个让他的人回来的交易
He just wants to orchestrate a deal where his guys come back;
让他们投票和赞恩合并  我们就不存在了
they vote to merge with Zane; and we cease to exist.
首席翻译官
█ 网易见外
我刚发现我的两个合伙人
I just found out that my two partners,
艾瑞克·卡尔多和艾伦·兰德
Eric Kaldor and Ellen Rand,
首席校对官
人人译视界
·
人人
居然背后捅我刀子
were willing to stab me in the back.
我们之后都不需要性爱手机了
We don't need the sex phone anymore,
因为你正中红心
because you hit the bull's-eye.
翻译     Alex 辰星晓Reginamoon 木浅 arcadiachi huiyi
天啊  我的精子没问题
Oh, my God. My boys can swim!
我遇到了法律问题  是个人私事
I've got a legal situation, and it's personal.
翻译     阿序 不見曦月 海云生 异羽 苏葵 小食人魔
也就是说你想让我派一个我们的律师过去
Which means you need me to send one of ours your way.
我想让亚历克斯·威廉姆斯来
I was thinking Alex Williams.
我猜你选亚历克斯而不是萨曼莎
I'm guessing firm harmony is why
校对     木浅
是出于律所和谐的原因
you want Alex and not Samantha.
有这方面的考虑  也是因为和案子情况有关
That, and a little of the nature of the case.
我例假来了  我没有怀孕
I got my period. I'm not pregnant.
时间轴     张小满    Caroline
-但那个测试说...  -那个是假阳性
- But the test said-- - It was a false positive.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
后期     斯人
总监     木浅
萨曼莎·惠勒
Samantha Wheeler.
通常情况下我很乐意见到一位前同事
Normally I'm happy to see a former colleague,
只要不是带着我们一半业务跑路的那位
just not one that walked out the door with half our business.
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端
唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
┌
┐
└
┘
那你接下来肯定会更不爽
Then you're really gonna hate it
因为我要攻击你们剩下的那点业务
when I attack what little business you have left.
-你要起诉灰度  -不是我
- You're suing Grayscale. - I'm not.
-是联邦政府  -扯淡
- The federal government is. - Bullshit.
你不能代理联邦政府
You don't represent the federal government.
根据《虚假申报法案》
According to the False Claims Act,
如果一家公司欺骗了国家
if a company defrauds the United States,
任何一位律师都能起诉以挽回损害
any attorney can sue to reclaim those damages.
随你怎么逼逼那些法案
You can spout any act you want;
你才不在乎什么美国政府
there's no way you give a shit about the U.S. Government.
没错  我确实不在乎  但我在乎
You're right--I don't-- but what I do care about
灰度的辩护代理权能不能像
is Grayscale Defense coming over to us
他们所希望的那样来到我们手上
like they wanted to in the first place.
他们才不想跟你们走呢
They never wanted to go anywhere with you.
那你为什么要用五年协议绑着他们
Then why are you holding them to their five-year agreement?
你不用回答  我俩都心知肚明
And before you answer, we both know,
这是因为如果你放手的话  他们会走的
it's because if you let them go, they'd leave.
也许吧  但如今你在起诉他们
Well, they might have, but now that you're suing them,
正好把灰度推向了我这边
you just tipped the Grayscales my way.
我都忘了你爱说俏皮话了
I forgot you and your puns.
如今我不再需要假装它们很有趣了
Well, I don't have to pretend they're charming, anymore.
接下来这样
So this is how it's gonna go.
我会把你吃得死死的
I'm gonna get you in a bear hug,
你唯一的出路就是放他们来我们这边
and your only way out is gonna be to let them come to us.
你可以立马动手  也可以等下再动
So you can do it now or you can do it later,
但相信我
but trust me:
这事已经板上钉钉了
it's gonna happen.
谢谢你的到访  萨曼莎
Thank you for stopping by, Samantha.
我都已经忘了自从你走后这里和谐了多少
I'd forgotten how much nicer it is here since you've been gone.
路易  你还在这里干什么呢
Louis, what are you still doing here?
我请了一天假
I took the day off.
然后我还给你办公室打了电话...
And I called your office...
也帮你请了一天假
you're taking the day off too.
-但是...  -没有"但是"
- But... - No "Buts."
希拉  我要带你去世界上最快乐的地方
Sheila, I am taking you to the happiest place on Earth.
路易  尽管我很爱威廉斯堡殖民地
Louis, as much as I love Colonial Williamsburg,
但今天不行
I can't today.
但我们的戏服都已经搬到车上了
But our costumes are already in the car.
谢谢你  路易
I appreciate that, Louis,
你想分散我的注意力这点真的很贴心
and it's sweet you want to distract me from... what happened,
但我今天本来就打算请假的
but I was already planning on taking today off anyway.
-是吗  -嗯
- You were? - Yeah.
路易...
Louis...
之前那个是假阳性  如果我们想要真阳性
we had a false positive, and if we want a real positive,
我们就不能继续碰运气了
we have to stop leaving things to chance.
所以我预约了
So I made an appointment
国内最好的生育专家
with the top fertility specialist in the country.
你真的觉得我们需要专家吗
You really think we need a specialist?
我觉得这些东西都是需要时间的
I think these things can take time,
所以我们越早得到帮助
so the sooner we get some help,
就能越早抱上孩子
the sooner we can hold that baby in our arms.
那我们还等什么呢  走吧
Well, then what are we waiting for? Let's go.
路易  你不用陪我去
Louis, you don't have to come.
希拉  听我说
Sheila, listen to me.
这事对我而言也一样重要
This is as important to me as it is to you,
而且这个世上
and there is nothing on this Earth
没有什么能阻止我陪在你身边
that's gonna stop me from being by your side.
萨曼莎  我能和你聊聊吗
Samantha, can I talk to you for a second?
说实话我现在有点忙
To tell you the truth, I'm a little busy right now.
你的意思是  你正忙着逼迫艾瑞克·卡尔多
What you mean is, you're a little busy leveraging Eric Kaldor
把他的一个客户给我们
into giving us one of his clients.
没错  我就是这个意思
Yeah, that's what I said.
你觉得这是个玩笑吗
You think this is funny?
我只觉得如今罗伯特遭遇了一些事情
What I think is Robert has been going through something,
而我希望在他回来时给他一份礼物
and I want to get him a little present for when he gets back.
换句话说  你听说罗伯特和亚历克斯
In other words, you heard Robert and Alex bonded
因为某事产生了亲密联系
over whatever he's been going through.
你觉得自己处境受到威胁
You feel your chair at the table is moving down,
所以你想要巩固自己的地位
and you're trying to move it back up.
是又如何
So what if I am?
搞定那个客户就是你给他最好的见面礼
Then the present you get him better be that client,
因为不用我告诉你
because I shouldn't have to tell you,
艾瑞克·卡尔多非等闲之辈
Eric Kaldor is no lightweight.
我没记错的话  我接什么案子不关你的事
And last I checked, the cases I take aren't your concern.
如果影响到律所的战绩
They are if there's a possibility
我就不能袖手旁观了
they could affect this firm's record,
所以如果你中意这个客户  你最好能拿下
so if you take this guy on, you better win.
这不成问题
And that won't be a problem
因为我清楚卡尔多的想法
because I know how Kaldor thinks.
我相信你  但现在
I'm sure you do, but in this instance,
你是要向一个
you picked a fight with the one person
求胜心胜于你的人发起挑战
who wants to beat you more than you want to beat him.
我已经发起挑战了
And I already picked this fight,
我现在可不会退缩
and I'm not backing down now,
所以除非你想直接命令我
so unless you want to give me a direct order
虽然我也不会听你的
that I wouldn't follow anyway,
我建议你别挡我的路  我还有案子要赢
I suggest you get out of my way, 'cause I got a case to win.
*看到钱  就愿意留下吃饭*
* See the money, wanna stay for your meal *
*给你太太再拿块馅饼*
* Get another piece of pie for your wife *
*所有人都想知道那感觉*
* Everybody wanna know how it feel *
*所有人都想见见那景象*
* Everybody wanna see what it's like *
*豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
* I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind *
*我和妹子忙着赚钱*
* Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money *
*好了*
* All right *
*退开点  我要跳舞*
* All step back, I'm 'bout to dance *
诉讼双雄  第八季  第八集
*美钞爵士摇摇摇*
* The greenback boogie *
路易·利特
高级合伙人
总算来了
There you are.
格雷琴  路易到底跑哪去了
Gretchen, where the hell is Louis?
你可以试试见面先客套些
You wanna try that again with some civility?
-客套什么  -比如说
- Some what, now? - How about,
"早上好  格雷琴  你今天看上去真棒"
"Good morning, Gretchen, you look lovely today.
-我给你带了杯拿铁  -你说得对
- I bought you this fine latte." - You're right.
我的时间迫在眉睫
I'm coming up against a deadline,
但也不能因此丢了礼貌
but that's no excuse to be rude.
早上好  格雷琴
Good morning, Gretchen.
你今天看起来真棒
Don't you look lovely today?
现在  感觉是不是好多了
Now, didn't that feel better?
确实如此  如果你能告诉我路易在哪儿
Actually, it did, and it'll feel even more better
我感觉会更好一些
when you tell me where Louis is.
我不太确定
I'm not so sure it will.
-路易今天不来  -该死
- Louis is gone for the day. - Shit.
发生了什么
What's the problem?
白山水正在考虑一个
White Mountain Water's putting together
在全国分销的协议
a national distribution deal,
为了结此事  我们须同意
and to close, we have to agree
一年内不能代理任何竞争对手分销商
not to rep any competing distributors for a year.
你需要路易同意这样的承诺
And you need Louis' approval for a commitment like that.
他已经同意了
He already agreed to it.
我只是需要他的签字
I just need his signature,
但我今天结束前就要
but I need it by the end of the day,
否则协议就没法达成了
or the whole deal could fall apart.
现在该我说"该死"了
Now it's my turn to say, "Shit."
格雷琴  我需要他的签字
Gretchen, I need that signature.
你会拿到的
And you will get it.
我说"该死"因为我知道我要去哪儿找他
I'm saying "Shit" 'cause I know where I have to go.
格雷琴...
Gretchen...
亚历克斯  把文件交给我吧
Alex, just give me the document.
告诉我文件要送到哪儿
Tell me where you need me to send it.
我向你保证  我会送过去的
I give you my word, it'll get there.
黄瓜水还是桉树水
Cucumber or eucalyptus?
-两个都有吗  -这里一应俱全
- They have both? - They have everything.
你看到等候室了吗  真皮座椅
Did you see the waiting room? Leather seats,
柔和灯光...
soothing lighting...
我还没见到这家伙就已经喜欢上他了
I haven't met the guy but I love him already.
赛斯女士  利特先生
Ms. Sazs, Mr. Litt.
麦克玛纳斯医生
Dr. McManus.
感谢你能临时安排和我们见面
Thank you so much for seeing us on such short notice.
不用喊我"医生"
Oh, please, no "Doctor" necessary.
我叫查尔斯  但是大家都叫我...
I'm Charles, but everybody calls me...
查斯
Chaz.
-查斯·麦克玛纳斯  -没错
- Chaz McManus. - That's right.
通常人们会猜"查克"
Usually people guess "Chuck."
我拿到你的病历表了
Now, I have your files,
但我更想亲自做个初始的健康状况
but I prefer to establish a baseline health myself.
-这样可以吗  -当然可以
- Is that okay? - Of course.
你需要我怎么做
Uh, what do you need me to do?
首先需要抽取一些血样
So we'll start with some blood samples--
沿着走廊到头就行
just head down that hall,
护士会指路给你  等你回来
the nurse will show you the way--and when you're back,
我们再来讨论你们
we can discuss everything the two of you
-想要讨论的事  -好的
- would like to accomplish. - Okay.
待会儿见
I'll see you in a bit.
很抱歉  请问您是不是
I'm sorry, do you not, uh...
不记得我了
remember me?
-我  -我是路易·利特
- I, uh... - Louis Litt.
斯卡斯代尔高中  88级的
Scarsdale High, class of '88.
抱歉  我真的不记得你了  路易
I'm sorry, I don't remember you, Louis.
我从没真正
You know, I never really felt like
在高中有过归属感
I fit in much during high school.
我更愿意不去想那些日子
I don't really think about those days.
但我也清楚  那时候我并不是个好孩子
But I also know I wasn't the nicest kid back then,
因此如果我俩在那会儿有任何嫌隙
so if there's any bad blood between us,
希望你别往心里去
I hope there's no hard feelings.
她就那样躺着  脚搁在马镫支架上
So there she was, feet in the stirrups.
路易在照顾她  俩人都穿着病号服
Louis is looking, both of them in hospital gowns...
等下  为什么路易也穿着病号服
Wait, why was Louis in a gown?
他不想让她因为穿病号服而感到难堪
He didn't want her to feel self-conscious.
还挺暖的
Oh, that's actually kind of sweet.
你是没在现场才能说出这话
You only get to say that because you weren't there,
我本来不应该告诉你的
and I shouldn't have to remind you,
但那病号服背后是没系上的
those gowns don't close in the behind...
所以在路易和希拉之间
So between Louis and Sheila,
我都是这么把文件递过去的
I had to walk that document in like this.
行了行了
Come on.
她真的上支架了呀
Was she really in the stirrups?
他们进医院前我瞥见了
I caught them before they went in the building,
但那会儿我心思全在某个电影上
but there was a movie that was playing in my head,
所以我只能说  情况不妙
so as far as I'm concerned, it's just as bad.
不管怎么说  重要的是亚历克斯拿到了签名
Well, the important thing is Alex got his signature
分数还是
and the score remains
格蕾琴胜世界一千万倍
Gretchen, 1,000,973; world, zero.
太对了
Damn right.
祝你好运  红毛
Good luck with your stack, Red.
你也是  格蕾琴
You too, Gretchen.
对了  不管你做什么
Oh, and whatever you do,
都别再去看那场电影了
try not to buy another ticket to that movie.
你就非要说出来
She just had to say that.
卡尔多先生
Mr. Kaldor.
距离庭审的既定时间还有两周
This trial is not scheduled for another two weeks,
你最好是有个好理由把我们叫来
so you'd better have a good reason for calling us here.
我的确有  法官大人  我希望您
I do, Your Honor. I would like you
能够撤销惠勒小姐出庭的资格
to remove Ms. Wheeler from this case.
-什么理由  -理由就是  你是
- On what grounds? - On the grounds that you were
我的委托人的正式出庭律师
an attorney of record for my client.
-这是真的吗  惠勒小姐  -坚决否认
- Is that true, Ms. Wheeler? - Absolutely not.
我从没参与过他们的案子
I never worked on their case.
根据这张账单
Well, according to this billing sheet,
你绝对有参与其中
uh, you absolutely did.
那只是两个小时的案子  还是七年前的
This was seven years ago for two hours.
法官大人  那时我还是个新律师
Your Honor, I was an associate.
一定是有人让我去
Someone must have told me to
复印了账单发给他们
run some copies and bill it to them.
一分钟之前你还说从没为他们工作过
A minute ago you had never worked for them at all,
现在又说给他们复印东西了
and now it's just running copies?
-法官大人  -这是你的账单没错吧
- Your Honor... - This is your billing sheet, isn't it?
这也是你的签名  没问题吧
I mean, this is your signature, isn't it?
是的  但就算我真的为灰度工作过
Yes, but even if I technically worked for Grayscale,
我从没有过获得保密信息的权限
I never had access to privileged information.
除非你在账单的问题上撒了谎
And unless you're lying about your billables--
顺便提一句  这句指控可是能吊销执照的
a disbarrable offense, by the way--
那么不管怎么说你都是受保密条例约束的
then technically or not you're bound by privilege.
综上  法官大人  她应当被禁止
And, Your Honor, she's prohibited
向曾经的委托人提起诉讼
from bringing a suit against an old client.
我想他说的对  惠勒小姐
I'm afraid he's right, Ms. Wheeler,
因此除非在贵律所存在
so unless there's someone else from your firm
不受保密条例约束的员工  我宣布该案撤销
not bound by privilege, this case is dismissed.
路易  你这个狗东西
Louis, you little piece of shit.
你竟然打小报告说我生物考试作弊
You ratted me out for cheating in bio?
没错  我打了
You're right, I did.
因为你做的事不地道
Because it isn't fair what you did,
而且欧康纳先生按照曲线打分的
and Mr. O'Connor grades on a curve.
你小子敢顶嘴
That sounded like talk-back.
全因为你  现在欧康纳没给我通过
Now, because of you, O'Connor gave me an "F,"
我老爹准备打死我
and my old man is gonna kill me.
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what that means?
意味着接下来全年的作业你都得帮我做了
You're gonna do my homework for the rest of the year,
而且一个字都不许往外说
and you're not gonna say a word about it anyone.
不  我拒绝  我不会向淫威屈服的
No, I'm not, and you can't make me.
抱歉  你可能没听到
I'm sorry, maybe you weren't listening?
我对生物一窍不通  也就是说我根本不知道
I don't know bio, which means I don't know
肾脏到底在哪个犄角旮旯
where the kidneys are.
现在我问你是在这儿  这儿  还是这儿
Now, are they here, here, or here?
你还要不要为了帮我写作业而良心不安
You still have philosophical reservations against helping me?
好好好  我做就是了  放我走吧
Okay, I'll do it! Just please let me go!
这才乖嘛
That's my boy.
每天第一次铃响之前
Every day before first bell,
当天的作业必须交到我手上
that day's homework is in my hands.
你敢迟交
You're ever late,
我就会请你去设备柜喝杯茶
we're gonna take a trip down to the equipment locker
带你去体育馆的器材室  把你关进去
in front of the whole school, and I'm gonna lock you in.
后来那一年我都天天跑去学校
Spent the rest of the year racing to school,
害怕自己迟到
just terrified I'd be late.
我第一次迟到时
First time I was...
查斯兑现了他的承诺
Chaz was true to his word.
把我拖进体育馆
Dragged me to the gym,
并推我进一个器材室
shoved me into an equipment locker...
跟我说要是我告诉别人
and said that if I ever told anyone,
下一次只会更糟
next time would be worse.
路易  你告诉过我你小时过得不好
Louis, you've told me what a hard time you had in your youth,
但这事
but this...
我一直都不去想这段过去
Ah, that's not even the part that I've been thinking about.
你看  到最后
You see, by the end...
我停止了反抗
I just stopped fighting.
要是我迟到了  查斯就跟我走过学校大厅
So if I was late, Chaz would walk me down the hall,
带我去体育馆
get to the gym.
他打开器材室的门
He'd open up the equipment locker door...
我就会把他的作业给他
I'd hand him his homework...
然后自己走进去
and I would walk myself right in.
我能想象出你这么久后
I can only imagine what you must have felt
再次见到他的感觉
when you saw him again after all this time.
他对这个只说了句"请别往心里去"
All he had to say about it was, "No hard feelings."
你的确往心里去了
Well, there are hard feelings.
你一直都记在心里
Feelings you have been carrying with you ever since.
因此
That's why...
我想给你看看这个
I wanna show you this.
三十年来我都没用再看过它一眼
It's something that I haven't looked at in 30 years.
路易  你给希拉看这个时  她怎么说
Louis, what did Sheila say when you showed her this?
给她看  不  我不能这么做
Show her? No, I couldn't do that.
-为什么  -因为我们一离开诊所
- Why not? - 'Cause I've been doing research
我就在做调查
since the minute we left the clinic,
希望这不是真的
hoping that it wasn't true,
但他是最好的
but there's nobody better than this guy.
要是我们想尽可能有个孩子
If we want our best chances to have this baby,
我只能处理好这些
I just have to deal with these...
感情
feelings.
那至少告诉希拉
Then at least let Sheila in
你的经历
on what you're going through,
因为你不疏导出去一些的话
because if you don't let off some steam,
早晚会爆炸的
there is likely to be an explosion.
哈维  抱歉打扰
Harvey? I'm sorry to bother you,
能占用你点时间吗
but do you have a minute?
难以置信
I don't believe this.
你案子不顺利
Shit went sideways with your case already
-跑来找我求助  -我可没这么说
- and you want my help. - I didn't say that.
你用不着说  因为你在这里
You didn't need to, 'cause you're here
用你"把黄油递给我"的腔调说话
with your "Pass the butter" Voice,
我早就警告过你这事可能发生
and I warned you this would happen.
-也许你的确警告了  但  -没有"也许"
- Maybe you did, but... - Not "Maybe."
我说过"你招惹错了人"
I said, "You're picking a fight with the wrong guy,"
你说你知道自己在干什么
and you said you knew what you were doing.
好吧  哈维
Okay, Harvey.
你是对的
You were right.
你现在是想说"告诉过你了"
Now you wanna say "I told you so,"
还是想帮我打败这家伙
or do you wanna help me beat this guy?
你才不会想知道我想做什么呢
You don't wanna know what I want to do,
但既然我不能做想做的  只能帮你了
but since I can't do that, I guess I have to help you.
要是你想给来我一下
And if what you're wanting to do is to take a swing at me,
我们解决完这事可以去一下拳击场
we can take this into the ring once we're done.
我是说我想把你的嘴粘起来
I meant I want to tape your mouth shut,
但我听你大谈拳击
but I heard you talk a big game with your boxing,
相信我  你不会想尝试的
and trust me-- you don't want a piece of this.
我不止是打拳击  哈维  我会跆拳道
I don't just box, Harvey, I kickbox,
我的腿比你的胳膊强壮五十倍
and my leg is 50 times stronger than your arm.
你之所以卷进这堆糟心事
And picking fights outside of your weight class
就是因为你挑战了和你不是同一重量级的选手
is how you got into this mess in the first place,
你是想知道怎么摆脱麻烦
so you wanna figure out how to get out of it?
还是想编织
Or you wanna make up fairytales
你痛扁我一顿的童话
about how you'd kick my ass?
我想知道怎么摆脱这个麻烦
I want to figure out how to get out of this.
那我们就上楼
Then we're gonna go upstairs
并且点一份超大加芝士的意大利辣肉肠
and order an extra-large pepperoni and cheese,
因为哪怕不是我挑起的这场战争
because I might not have picked this fight,
我也不可能让
but there is no way I am letting
艾瑞克·"我得理个发"·卡尔多
Eric "I need a haircut" Kaldor
占我的人上风
get the better of one of my people.
这是干什么
Oh, what is this for?
奖励你今天陪我
For being by my side today.
我当然在了  我告诉你我会在的
Of course. I told you that I would be.
的确让我很放松  而且我得说
Well, it really set me at ease, and I have to say,
查斯真是知识渊博
Chaz is so knowledgeable,
而且他的床边礼仪简直完美
and his bedside manner is a dream.
是啊
Right.
他是最好的
He's the best.
有他插在我们俩之间
We're gonna be swimming in babies by the time
我们马上就子女成群了
he's through with us.
路易  怎么了
Louis, what's wrong?
查斯在高中时欺负过我
Chaz was my bully in high school.
三年级时他折磨了我整个学年
He... tortured me my entire junior year.
太糟糕了
That's awful.
你怎么没告诉我
Why didn't you say something to me?
因为那都是30年前的事了  希拉
Because it was 30 years ago, Sheila.
我不会让高中的陈年旧事
I'm not gonna let something from high school
阻止我们去见全国最好的生育专家
keep us from seeing the best fertility specialist in the country.
路易  我们可以找第二好的
Louis, we can find whoever's second best.
不  不可以
No, we can't.
如果那样没成功的话
If it didn't work out,
我永远都不会原谅我自己
I would never forgive myself.
-我能应付得了  -你确定吗
- I can handle it. - Are you sure?
相信我
Trust me...
我会没事的
I'll be okay.
卡拉  我收到你的信息了
Carla, I got your message.
我以最快速度赶来了
I came as soon as I could.
那你该用我们付给你的巨额费用
Then you need to use that huge retainer we pay you
去买一辆更快的车
to buy a faster car,
因为我得知我们已经没有分销合同了
'cause I found out we no longer have a distribution deal.
你在说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
你说已经跟我们达成合约的经销商
Our distributor that you said we had a done deal with
来电说他们得到了更好的报价
called to say that they got a better offer.
如果他们这么快就得到了竞争性报价
And if they have a competing offer that fast,
那么他们一直都是在欺诈性谈判
they've been negotiating in bad faith this whole time.
我不在乎他们怎么做的
I don't give a shit what they've been doing.
我想知道你会怎么做
I want to know what you're gonna do about it.
我会提醒他们唯一
I'm gonna remind them the only way
能跟我们解除合同的情况
they can break our deal is
就是在签名没送到的前提下
if that signature didn't get over there,
如果他们想因为别的理由而食言的话
and if they try to back out for any other reason...
你还不明白吗
Don't you get it?
根本没有别的理由
There is no other reason.
他们说签名根本就没送到过
They're saying that signature never got there.
卡拉  我告诉你
Carla, I'm telling you,
签名已经送到了
that signature got there,
我不可能让他们食言的
and they're not backing out of anything.
你说的最好是对的
You'd better be right,
因为我们公司的未来就指望这次扩张了
because our future is based on this expansion,
像我说过的  你告诉过我这事已经谈妥了
and like I said, you told me it was a done deal.
格蕾琴  告诉我你今天把路易的签名邮过去了
Gretchen, tell me you sent Louis' signature over there today.
我邮了  怎么了
I did. Why?
他们说没收到
They're saying they never got it.
纯属扯淡
Well, that's some Grade-A bullshit.
快递员今天下午来取货的
The courier came and took it this afternoon.
那要么是快递员没把签名送到
Then either the courier failed to deliver it...
要么是这些人在睁眼说瞎话
Or these guys are straight-up lying.
不管怎样  我需要你帮我
Either way, I need you to get me
从快递员那弄一张收据
a receipt from that courier.
我明天交给你
Then you'll have it by tomorrow.
别担心  我们能搞定这事
Don't worry, we'll fix this.
谢谢  格蕾琴
Thanks, Gretchen.
很感谢你对这事这么上心
I appreciate you being all over this.
等一下
Hold on.
如果我们能证明你没联系过灰度公司
If we can prove you never had any contact with Grayscale,
那么我们就能说并没有特权关系
we can argue no privileged relationship existed.
是个办法  但就算我们把当时的人都传唤来
It's an idea, but even if we subpoena everybody from back then,
他们也不感兴趣帮我洗脱罪名好让我告他们
it's not in their interests to clear me so I can sue them.
还有  卡尔多可以说这根本不重要
Plus, Kaldor... could still say it doesn't matter
因为你看过机密信息
because you saw confidential information.
那人真是个混蛋
Goddamn that man.
我只是想帮罗伯特找个新客户
All I wanted was to get Robert another client.
我知道  你是个圣人
I know. You're a saint,
你做的一切都是上帝的旨意
and all you were doing was God's work.
好了  你别说个没完了
All right, you don't have to rub it in.
如果我们今晚想找点乐子我就得说
I do if we're gonna have any fun tonight.
说到找乐子  已经这么晚了
Speaking of fun, it's late;
我们刚分享了一个披萨  是时候问问了
we just shared a pizza; I have to ask.
你和罗伯特是什么情况
What is it with you and Robert?
我是不会跟你谈论罗伯特的事的
I'm not talking about me and Robert with you.
所以你可以跟唐娜聊私生活
Oh, so you can tell Donna about yourself
但是跟我就不行
but you can't tell me?
你知道我们约会了
You know we went out?
我当然知道  我无所不知
Of course I do. I know everything.
就连那次你想要
Even the time that you tried to...
不  你一无所知
No. You don't know anything.
你只是想让我说漏嘴
You're just trying to get me to spill the beans
因为唐娜不肯告诉你
because Donna wouldn't.
就算是这样又如何
So what if I am?
我当时跟你说的也是这句话
Hmm, that's exactly what I said to you
在你因为亚历克斯发现我干这事的时候
when you called me out on doing this because of Alex.
"就算是这样又如何"
"So what if I am?"
也许我们比你想象中更加相像
Maybe we're more alike than you thought after all.
在你刚来到这里的时候
And that's what you tried telling me
你就想告诉我这件事
when you first got here.
那晚在我的办公室
That night in my office,
你对我竖中指
when you flipped me the bird.
据我回忆  你对我也竖中指了
As I recall, you flipped it right back.
-是的  也许我们的确  -等一会
- Yeah, well, maybe we really are... - Wait a second.
"比我们想象中更加相像"
"More alike than we thought."
如果并不只是你我之间呢
What if it's not just you and me?
-你想到什么了  -卡尔多
- What do you got? - Kaldor.
他说我可以避开账单的唯一办法
He said the only way I could get around
是说我对这个撒谎了
the billing sheet was to say I lied about it.
但是如果他才是那个撒谎的人
But what if he's the one who lied,
那张单子从未存在过呢
and that sheet never existed?
看起来有人需要去拜访艾瑞克·卡尔多了
Looks like someone needs to pay a visit to Eric Kaldor.
你认为你可以处理吗
You think you can handle it?
我为什么要处理
Why would I handle it?
因为
Because...
你在你不必要的时候帮助了我
you helped me when you didn't have to,
然后你说你只是想找点乐子
and you just said you wanted to have some fun.
有什么比黏着艾瑞克·卡尔多
And what better way to have some fun
更好的找乐子的办法呢
than sticking it to Eric Kaldor?
我明白了  你不仅想得到罗伯特的礼物
I get it. You don't just want to get Robert a present.
你想要让我亲自为你的成功投资
You want to get me personally invested in your success.
所以如果我这样做了呢
So what if I do?
好的  萨曼莎  我来搞定艾瑞克
Okay, Samantha. I'll take care of Eric.
但是在我们今晚结束之前
But before we call it a night,
你提出的这个想法说明你和他一样
this idea came from you suggesting you're like him,
然后你开始说伪造证据
and then you started talking about fabricating evidence...
答案是不  哈维
The answer is no, Harvey.
我此生从未捏造过证据
I've never fabricated evidence in my life.
你好  我在你们这寄了包裹我需要发票
Hi, I need a receipt for a package I sent with your service.
当然可以  你的订单编号是
Of course. What's your order number?
"1-2-6-5-7."
我们的记录显示那个包裹没有在这寄出
Our records show that package was never sent.
你的记录是错的
Well, your records are wrong,
因为你在和一个寄了这个包裹的女人说话
because you're speaking to the woman who sent it.
对不起  女士  我不知该对这说什么
I'm sorry, ma'am. I don't know what to say to that.
什么话也不用说  把我转接给快递
Don't say anything. Just put me through to the courier.
女士  如果我们的系统里没记录
Ma'am, if there's no record in our system,
和快递联系也是没有用的
talking to him isn't going to help.
我们的快递员现在很忙
And our couriers are extremely busy,
-我没有时间来  -听着  小姑娘
- and I don't have time to... - Listen here, young lady.
你觉得我不忙吗  我也很忙
You don't think I'm busy? I am.
但是没有忙到找不到你住哪
But not too busy to find out where you live,
你妈妈的娘家姓  和其他任何事
your mother's maiden name, and anything else
这能让你的生活变成人间炼狱
that it takes to make your life a living hell
如果你不把我转接给那个该死的快递
if you don't put me through to that goddamn courier.
我试试能不能联系上他
I'll see if I can connect him.
-你好  -勒罗伊  谢天谢地是你
- Hello? - Leroy. Thank God it's you.
是我
Yep, it's me, all right.
我理解你在取件上出了问题
I understand there is a problem with your pick-up.
当然有问题  今天中午我在我桌子上
There sure is. I left a package for you
给你留了个包裹
this afternoon on my desk.
我知道你拿走了它因为它不见了
I know you picked it up because it's gone.
对不起  格雷琴  它不在我这
Sorry, Gretchen, it wasn't there.
我等了  差不多  10分钟
I waited around, like, for ten minutes.
我问了前台  她那没有  所以我走了
I asked the receptionist, and she didn't have it, so I left.
谢谢  勒罗伊
Thank you, then, Leroy.
谢谢你的时间  不好意思给你添麻烦了
Th--thanks for your time. Sorry to put you out.
没关系
No problem.
唐娜·保尔森  首席运营官
你好  你一定是蜜西
Hello. You must be Missy.
对的  你是
That's right. And you are...
桑迪·麦克拉斯基的朋友
A friend of Sandy McClusky's,
之前管这张桌子的女人
the woman who used to cover this desk.
我记得桑迪
I remember Sandy.
她培训的我
She trained me.
试图  无论如何
Well, tried to, anyway.
桑迪和我一起从约翰逊·鲍威尔打拼出来
Sandy and I came up together in the pool
连同丽贝卡·哈特和帕特·尼科尔斯
at Johnson Powell along with Rebecca Hart and Pat Nichols.
我们一起经历了很多
We went through a lot together.
这些和我有什么关系
And how does that have anything to do with me?
在她退休之前欠我个人情
Sandy owed me a favor before she retired, and...
-我需要她还这个人情  -那去联系她
- I need to call it in. - So call her.
她在科勒尔盖布尔斯
Well, she's in Coral Gables.
你是现在在这个职位上的人
You're the one on this desk now,
所以这个人情轮到你还
so the favor falls to you.
我需要你记录下你昨天收到了这个
I need you to log that you received this yesterday.
问题是
The problem with that
我每天没收到这个
is I didn't receive it yesterday.
只是个意外
It was an honest mistake.
是不是意外  都是你的问题
Honest or not, it's yours.
-为什么我要帮你掩盖呢  -因为桑迪欠我
- Why should I cover for you? - Because Sandy owed me.
这就是我们彼此关照对方的方式
That's how we take care of each other.
在你出生之前就一直如此了
It's been going on since before you were born.
你兑换这人情的机会从她离开那时就没了
And your chance to cash in that favor walked out when she did.
听我说  小姑娘
Listen to me, young lady...
不  你听我说
No, you listen to me.
你这是在叫我对我的老板撒谎
You're asking me to lie to my boss,
我不会这么做的  所以
and I'm not gonna do it, so...
比起来这
instead of coming in here,
试图让我的工作陷入危机
trying to get me to put my ass on the line
去尊重一个什么80年前的传统
to honor some 80-year-old tradition,
为什么你不在一开始就不搞砸这件事呢
why don't you not screw up in the first place?
你以为自己很了不起  你不需要任何人
You think you're hot shit, and you don't need anyone...
但是有一天你将会处在我现在的情况中的
but one day you're gonna be in the position that I'm in,
然后你会很后悔自己没有人际网络
and you're gonna wish like hell you had a network of people
-可以求助  -也许我会
- to call on for help. - Maybe I will.
但是我感觉  在那之前
But something tells me by then...
你早就不在了
you'll be long gone.
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.
别告诉我  你接了这个
Don't tell me. You're picking up the case
我让萨曼莎推掉的案子  而我
I had Samantha booted off of, and now I'm...
现在该瑟瑟发抖了
supposed to be shaking with fear.
你以为我会这么简单地放过你吗  艾瑞克
You think I'd let you off that easy, Eric?
-不可能  -你在说什么
- Not a chance. - What are you talking about?
有一个成语叫做
There's an old saying:
贼喊捉贼
accuse the other side of that which you are guilty.
还有一个成语叫做简明扼要
There's another old saying: get to the point.
你说萨曼莎在请款单的问题上说了谎
You said Samantha lied about that billing sheet,
我们就想  是你在请款单的问题上说了谎
which got us thinking, you lied about that billing sheet,
而萨曼莎从未为灰度工作过
and Samantha never worked for Grayscale.
你要敢再重复一次  我就告你诽谤
And you say that again, and I will have you sued for slander.
那我就不说了  我直接证明
Then I won't say it. I'll just prove it.
你难道准备把手伸进我的大脑
You gonna reach into my brain
让我承认我从未做过的事情
to get me to admit to something I never did?
不  艾瑞克  我会传唤你寄出的所有账单
No, Eric. I'll subpoena every bill ever sent,
和萨曼莎提交的所有请款单
and every billing sheet ever submitted by Samantha,
如果它们不吻合
and when they don't add up,
我们就不需要这个案子继续
we won't need this case to move forward
因为你会因为捏造证据而被取消律师资格
because you'll be disbarred for fabricated evidence.
事情绝不会严峻到我们不得不把
There's no way I have to hand over
专属档案交给一家对手律所
proprietary records to a competing firm.
你真的想为了一个客户赌一赌这个可能性吗
You really want to take that chance over one client?
放弃吧  艾瑞克
Let this go, Eric.
结束了
It's over.
你不光想带走我的合伙人
So it's not enough you had to take my partner
我一半的生意
and half my business?
你还想要剩下的一半
You have to come after the rest?
我并没有这么想
I didn't come after anything.
既然你提起了这件事
But as long as we're talking,
我没有带走你的合伙人
I didn't take your partner.
是背着他试图偷走我们两家律所
You went behind his back to try to steal both our firms,
你别以为这点煽情的手段能有用
so if you think this little sob story is gonna move me,
你还不如拿一张餐巾纸
you might as well pick up a tissue,
擦擦你的眼泪  去找别人诉苦
dab your eyes, and tell it somewhere else.
等你演完了  你就可以去联系灰度公司
And when you're finished, you can call Grayscale
告诉他们  他们现在的律师是我
and let them know they're now represented by me.
格蕾琴
Gretchen.
你有什么事吗
What brings you into my office?
-我需要帮助  -让我猜猜
- I need help. - Let me guess:
你来找我是因为你听说我能解决问题
you're coming to me because you heard I fix things.
我找你是因为路易向你发火的时候
I'm coming because when Louis lost his mind on you,
你没跑去找罗伯特
you didn't run to Robert.
你去找了哈维  因为你知道他需要一个朋友
You went to Harvey, 'cause you knew he needed a friend.
现在你需要一个朋友
And right now you need a friend.
我搞砸了  捅了个大篓子
I screwed up, big-time.
没有寄出一份关键的文件
Didn't send a document that needed to be sent,
现在亚历克斯·威廉姆斯有了大麻烦
and now Alex Williams is gonna be in deep shit.
格蕾琴  我也许很能干
Gretchen, I may be good,
但是即使是我也不能帮你逆转过去
but I can't travel back in time for you.
我知道  我求那个该死的秘书
I know that. I asked that goddamn secretary
帮我找个借口  但是她不愿意遵守荣誉准则
to cover for me, but... she wouldn't honor the code.
所以你希望我帮你把事情
So you want me to make it look like
搞得像是她的错而不是你的
it's her fault and not yours.
是
That's right.
抱歉  我不能这样做
I'm sorry, I--I can't do it.
是因为我告诉你这可能波及亚历克斯吗
Is this because I told you it could hurt Alex?
这和亚历克斯没有关系
This has nothing to do with Alex.
我得告诉你  因为要解决这个问题
I'm telling you this because what it would take
可能导致结果会糟糕1000倍
to fix this thing could make it 1,000 times worse,
作为你的朋友  我得告诉你
and being your friend means telling you
-这不值得  -可是  萨曼莎
- it is not worth it. - But, Samantha...
没有”可是”  你需要去找亚历克斯
No "Buts." You need to go to Alex
告诉他真相  因为这是他的客户
and tell him the truth, because this is his client,
他有权知道
and he deserves to know.
路易  你在做什么  你要错过晚餐了
Louis, what are you doing? You're missing dinner.
今天的晚餐是调羹汉堡  我也没错过什么
It's sloppy Joe night, so I'm not missing anything.
不过你要是想知道  我在起草一份合同
But if you must know, I'm writing a contract.
什么  这是你的公民教育课的作业吗
What? Is that your civics homework or something?
不  埃斯特
No, Esther.
这是一份有法律约束力的文件  规定我需要
It's a legally binding document stipulating that I'm required
在本学年结束之前与查斯·麦克玛纳斯扯平
to get even with Chaz McManus by the end of the school year.
你是说因为他把你塞进了储物柜里
You mean because he's putting you in the locker.
是的埃斯特  就是这个意思
Yes, Esther, that's what I mean.
相信我  路易
Trust me, Louis.
不管你是想做什么
Whatever you're thinking of doing,
查斯只会让你的生活糟糕100倍
Chaz is just gonna make your life 100 times worse.
你又有多了解怎么面对一个恶霸
Like you'd know anything about dealing with a bully.
相信我  我知道
Believe me, I do.
你还记得我去年离开乐队吗
Remember when I dropped out of band last year?
你是说你告诉妈妈
You mean when you told Mom
你忍受不了和我相提并论的那一次吗
you couldn't stand being associated with me?
我忍受不了的是卡洛琳·普赖斯
What I couldn't stand was Carolyn Price
每天刁难我
picking on me every day.
-我不知道  -你现在知道了
- I didn't know that. - Well, now you do.
所以你到底想不想听我的建议
So do you want my advice or not?
想
I want it.
低调行事  听命与他
Lay low... do what he wants,
并祈祷他忘记你的存在
and hope he forgets you ever existed.
他不会忘记的  埃斯特
Well, he's not ever going to forget, Esther,
-我也不会  -路易  你还不明白吗
- and neither am I. - Louis, don't you get it?
像查斯这样的男生在高中总是能为所欲为
Guys like Chaz always get their way in high school.
但高中毕业后  你自己可能也不知道
But high school ends, and before you know it,
有一天你会成功  而他则在加油站帮你加油
you'll be successful, and he'll be pumping your gas.
我的天  你说的没错
Oh, my God. You're right.
我现在还没强大到能与他抗衡
I'm not powerful enough to face him now,
-但有一天  我会向他证明  -不  路易
- but someday I'll show him. - No, Louis,
-我不是这个意思  -不好意思
- that's not what I meant. - Now, excuse me.
我现在得修改我的合同
I need to reword my contract.
卡拉  我一会打给你
Carla, let me call you right back.
我们正需要的人刚走进我办公室
I think what we needed just walked into my office.
-她还在生气  -只要你交出收据
- She still pissed? - She won't be
她就不生气了
once you hand over that receipt.
问题就在这  亚历克斯  没有收据
That's just it, Alex. There isn't one.
-又来了  -我从未把文件寄过去
- Come again? - I never sent the documents over.
你在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you shitting me?
你现在才来告诉我这个
And you're just coming to me with this now?
我昨晚才意识到发生了什么
I just realized last night what happened.
那昨晚为什么不来找我
Then why didn't you come to me last night?
因为我以为我还能补救
Because I thought I could still fix it.
不不  我们来回顾一下
No, no. Let's just review:
你在跟我瞎扯了什么
after you gave me all that bullshit about,
'早上好  格雷琴  你看上去真帅'之后
"Good morning, Gretchen. Don't you look lovely,"
-你就他妈当着我的面撒谎  -我没撒谎
- you ----ing lied to my face. - It wasn't a lie.
我发现了以后  我试着去补救
When I found out, I tried to fix it.
你没有  当卡拉发现
Well, you didn't, and when Carla finds out
这事跟我有关
this was on me...
是我的错  我来承担
It's my fault. I'll take the bullet.
你来承担
Take the bullet?
他们才不管这是谁的错
They're not gonna give a shit whose fault this is.
这是我的委托人  就是我的错
It's my client. It's on my head.
我可以做些什么吗
Is there anything I can do?
从现在起  说到做到
From now on, do what you say you're gonna do,
如果因为某些原因做不到
and if for some reason you don't,
至少早点鼓起勇气告诉我  以免不可收拾
at least have the courage to tell me before it's too late.
我知道我们需要客户
I know we demanded the client,
但没想到你会亲自送他们上门
but I never imagined you'd hand-deliver them.
萨曼莎  我唯一送的东西
The only thing I'm delivering, Samantha,
-是最后通牒  -埃里克  发最后通牒
- is an ultimatum. - The thing about giving ultimatums, Eric,
需要占据上风  但你没有
is that you need to have the upper hand, and you don't.
我也想到了  然后我想到
Yeah, I thought that too. But then I thought about
哈维说过
what Harvey said, "Accuse the other side
贼喊捉贼
of that which you are guilty,"
我觉得这就是你对我做的
and I think that's what you did to me.
抱歉让你失望了  但是我从未伪造
Sorry to disappoint you, but I have never fabricated
-任何证据  -但你藏过
- any evidence. - No, but you buried some.
科曼公司
Corman Ventures.
那只是我帮罗伯特
That was just a personal case I took care of
办的一个私人案子
as a favor to Robert.
你做了违法的事情
And I think you broke the law to do it.
你少胡说八道
You don't know what you're talking about.
也许你没有  但是贝蒂·帕尔默有
Maybe not, but Betty Palmer does.
她离开时的情形
See, it always bothered me
总是萦绕在我心头
the circumstances around her leaving
-所以我给她打了个电话  -胡扯
- so I decided to give her a call. - Bullshit.
她不可能会告诉你
There's no way she'd talk to you.
你不如去珊瑚山墙区散个步亲自问她吧
Why don't you take a stroll on down to Coral Gables to find out?
问完之后  如果你不想让她把
And when you're finished, if you don't want her telling
告诉我的事情告诉全世界
the entire world what she told me,
你就把你最久的客户移交给我
you're gonna hand over your oldest client.
我不可能就这么把我最久的客户交给你
I'm not gonna just hand over my oldest client to you.
你会的  因为你要是让我
Well, I think you will, because you put me
见法官
in front of a judge--
'法官大人  我没有伪造任何东西
"Your Honor, I didn't fabricate anything.
一定是有人犯了笔误'
Someone must have made a clerical error."
她肯定抓住你的小辫子
She has got you dead to rights.
不  我们只是各执一词
No. It's her word against mine.
像哈维说的
Like Harvey said,
你真的想用一个案子
you know, you really want to take that chance
来冒险吗
over one piece of business?
希望明天早上能看到我新客户的资料
I'll expect my new client's information by tomorrow.
亚历克斯
Alex.
你说我们只需要走走过场
You said what we needed just walked in.
你是在说同样的废话 还是什么新把戏？
Are you walking in with the same line of bullshit or a new one?
卡拉 对不起
Carla, I am sorry.
沟通有点问题
There was a miscommunication.
文件没有寄出去
The document was never sent,
但我们可以解决它
but we can fix it.
如果我说完很欣赏你的诚实
I'd tell you I appreciate the honesty,
但那是在说谎 那个经销商
but I'd be lying. That distributor,
我的经销商 刚刚打电话来说
my distributor, just called to say
他们与竞争对手达成协议了
they closed with our competitor.
王八蛋
Son of a bitch.
没有给我们反击的机会？
They didn't give us a chance to counter?
我们就不应该走到要反击那步
We should never have had to counter.
你是对的
You're right.
我承担全责 我会帮你另找交易
I take responsibility and I'll find you another deal.
另找交易？我差不多就要
Another deal? I am this close
另找一家律师事务所了
to finding another law firm.
- 卡拉 - 你说沟通有问题
Carla. You said there was a miscommunication.
那么告诉我怎么回事 不许再骗我
So tell me what happened and don't you dare lie to me again.
我们的一位秘书搞砸了
One of our secretaries messed up.
她以为文件被拿走了
She thought the document had been picked up,
但其实没有
but it never was.
那么你想保住我的生意
Then if you wanna keep my business,
要做的就是解雇那个无能的秘书
what you're going to do is fire that incompetent secretary.
- 你好 贝蒂 - 萨曼莎
Hello, Betty. Samantha.
我知道你迟早会打电话来的
I knew you'd be calling sooner or later.
我不知道你怎么告诉埃里克的
I don't know what you've been telling Eric,
但你不能告诉其他任何人
but you're not gonna tell it to anyone else.
- 为什么？- 因为你签署了保密协议
And why is that? Because you signed an NDA.
跟公司签的保密协议 而不是跟你
And that NDA was with the firm, not you.
现在管事的是埃里克 而他没有说什么
And Eric's running it now, and he's not enforcing anything.
贝蒂 我给了你十万块和一份新工作
Betty, I got you a hundred thousand and a new job.
佛罗里达的房地产事务所
Working estate law in Florida.
好像我赢了彩票一样
You make it sound like I won the lottery
事实是我试图阻止你
when the truth is I tried to stop you
犯法
from committing a crime.
结果你不但不听 还把我赶出城外
Instead of listening, you ran me out of town.
我必须从零开始
I had to start my life again, from nothing.
我当时可能没有感觉到 但......
And I may not have felt bad about it at the time, but...
直到今天还困扰着我
it haunts me to this day.
你想要什么？更多钱？
So what is it you want? More money?
- 因为我可以 - 我不需要钱
Because I can-- I don't need money.
我想要毁了你的职业生涯 就像你毁了我的一样
What I want is to ruin your career like you ruined mine.
但我会满足的是我得到的
But what I'll settle for is what I got.
你面对的是兰德·卡尔多最新的初级合伙人
You are dealing with the newest Junior Partner at Rand Kaldor.
贝蒂 如果你帮他这样对我...
Betty, if you help him do this to me...
省省吧 上次只有我和你
Save your threats. Last time, it was just me and you.
这一次 我得到了埃里克·卡尔多的全力支持
This time, I have the full backing of Eric Kaldor.
而且他希望的回报跟我一样
And he wants some payback just as much as I do.
我猜客户反映不好
I'm guessing that the client didn't take it well.
格雷琴告诉你了
Gretchen told you.
亚历克斯 这是一个错误
Alex, it was a mistake.
我也有关
And I had something to do with it.
我知道你对她不爽
I know you're upset with her...
不仅仅是我不爽 白山说
It's not just me that's upset. White Mountain said
如果我们不解雇格雷琴 他们会另找高明
if we don't fire Gretchen, they'll walk.
你不会真的考虑......
You're not seriously considering...
不 我正另想办法
No. I'm trying to figure another way out,
但是现在 不行
but right now, I can't.
好吧 那么也许我们应该
Okay. Well, then, maybe we should--
见鬼 她怎么会把这搞砸了？
Goddamn it. How the hell did she mess this up?
这样 我知道丢了客户不是好事
Look, I know it's not great to lose a client.
- 但每个人都会遇到 - 在最糟糕的时候
But it happens to everybody. It's happening to me
发生在我身上 还要感谢她
at the worst time, thanks to her.
我不小心把路易斯签名的信从她桌子取走了
I took the envelope with Louis' signature off her desk by mistake.
她以为是快递员取走的
She thought the courier took it.
她应该检查一下
She should've checked.
她应该一知道
And she sure should've told me
马上就告诉我
the second she knew.
那你要怎么做？
So what are you gonna do?
我打电话给他们 免除他们
I'm gonna call them up, offer to waive their bill
上个季度的账单
for the last quarter,
希望足以让我保住这个该死的客户
and hope that's enough to keep my goddamn client.
你还好吗  路易
How you doing, Louis?
有点紧张  你呢
A little nervous. You?
有点紧张
Little nervous.
希拉  路易  谢谢你们能来
Sheila, Louis, thank you for coming in.
我们很惊讶你那么快就叫我们回来了
We're surprised you asked us to come back so soon.
我不想让你们担心  但是
Well, I didn't want to concern you, but...
我的天  是我的检查结果出了什么问题吗
Oh, God, is there something wrong with my test results?
都在掌控之中  你有一些子宫肌瘤
It's nothing we can't handle. You have some cervical fibroids
很不幸  你的妇产科医生疏忽了
that, unfortunately, your OB missed,
我希望能移除它们
and I'd like to remove them.
你是说做手术吗
You mean--you mean like surgery?
这只是个简单的门诊腹腔镜手术
It's just a simple outpatient laparoscopic procedure.
我做过上百次了
I've done it hundreds of times.
-那我觉得我们该做  -好极了
- Then I think we should do it. - Great.
我可以帮你们安排在下两周
Then I'll set something up in the next two weeks...
等等  希拉  也许我们该去问问别的医生
Hold on a minute. Shelia, maybe we should get a second opinion.
路易  你大可以去咨询别的医生
Louis, you're welcome to get a second opinion,
但我真的认为
but I really do think
我们应该先把手术预定了
we should go ahead and schedule the surgery now.
这样我们可以先把手术提上日程
That way we have it on the books...
声明下  我可是专业干这行的
And for the record, this is my area of expertise,
我真的认为
and I really do think that...
如果你知道怎样对你好
If you know what's good for you,
你就会进那个储物柜里
you'll get in that locker.
利特  我可以在你进去前先揍你一顿
Litt, I could punch you before you get in,
或者你可以乖乖进去
or you could just get in.
你是不是忘了什么
Aren't you forgetting something?
路易  你觉得这个计划如何
Well, Louis, what do you think of that plan?
我才不管你的专业领域是什么
I don't give a shit what your area of expertise is.
我们永远不会跟你预定任何手术
We're not gonna schedule a goddamn thing with you, now or ever,
如果你敢碰一下我心爱的女人
and if you lay one hand on the woman I love,
我向天发誓  一定把你打得满地找牙
I swear to God, I'll beat the shit out of you.
路易
Well, Louis...
你觉得这个计划如何
what do you think of that plan?
我想没有必要再看别的医生了
I see no reason why we need a second opinion.
-就按你的意见来  -好  那就这么定了
- We'll do whatever you say. - Great, then it's all settled.
萨曼莎
Hey, Samantha.
唐娜  不管什么事  我现在很忙
Donna, whatever it is, I'm kind of busy.
我看出来了
I can see that.
这和你临时推迟了三个客户的会议
Does it have anything to do with why you pushed
有什么关系吗
three client meetings at the last minute?
我不知道你还监视着我的一举一动
I didn't realize you kept such close tabs on my calendar.
我没有
I don't,
但当客户的律师不理睬他们时
but when those clients get brushed off by their lawyer,
他们就给我打电话
I'm the one they call.
我和他们说了  等我出差回来
And I told them those meetings will be back
那些会议都会重回议程的
on the books as soon as I'm back from my trip.
出什么差  你没有申请出差啊
What trip? You haven't submitted a travel request.
我也不会申请
And I won't be,
因为是私事
because this is personal.
这不会跟今天艾瑞克·卡尔多来有关系吧
Okay, does this have anything to do with Eric Kaldor coming here today?
只是我需要去趟佛罗里达州
It has to do with me needing to get down to Florida
你别告诉任何人
and you not telling anyone.
-萨曼莎  -唐娜  你别管了
- Samantha... - Donna, just let me do what I do.
让我捋清楚
Let me get this straight.
你希望我瞒着哈维和罗伯特一件
You want me to keep something from Harvey and Robert
我很确定会露馅的事
that I'm pretty sure might blow up
还不告诉我是什么
in both their faces without telling me what it is?
-是的  -我不知道自己能不能做到
- Yes, I do. - Well, I'm not sure I can do that.
你知道吗  唐娜
You know what, Donna?
如果你想告诉别人  去吧
If you wanna tell someone, go ahead.
没关系
Doesn't matter,
-反正我一定要上那趟飞机  -行
- 'cause I'm getting on that plane anyway. - Okay.
去赶你的飞机吧
Go ahead and catch your plane.
我只希望你知道自己在干什么
I just hope you know what you're doing.
无论你要去干什么  都不会发生了
Whatever you're up to, it's not gonna happen,
因为你不能上那飞机
'cause you're not getting on that plane.
-唐娜告诉你了  -你说对了
- Donna told you. - You're damn right
-唐娜告诉了我  -真不敢相信
- Donna told me. - I don't believe it.
-她让我误以为  -萨曼莎  当我问你
- She led me to think that... - Samantha, when I asked you
你是否伪造了证据时  你说没有
if you fabricated evidence, you said you hadn't,
我当时相信了你
and I believed you.
-现在我不信了  -哈维
- But now I think you have. - Harvey.
我觉得你伪造了证据
I think you fabricated evidence;
卡尔多抓住这个把柄威胁你
Kaldor is using it to blackmail you;
现在你准备去
and now you're about to head
某个地方阻止这事曝光
to wherever the hell you're going to stop it.
-你说忘了吗  -我说对了吗
- Are you finished? - Am I right?
我没有骗你
I didn't lie to you,
而且我从未伪造证据
and I never fabricated evidence.
那到底发生什么事了
What the hell's going on here?
五年前  我们接了一个案子
Five years ago, we had a case.
刑事案件
Criminal.
一个执行总裁的成年孩子被指控谋杀未遂
One of our CEO's adult children was charged with attempted murder.
药剂厂那家伙的女儿
The pharmaceutical guy's daughter.
就是她
That's the one.
我用了所有必要手段帮她脱罪
And I did what it took to get her out of it.
具体是什么手段
And what exactly did it take?
我隐藏了证据
I buried evidence.
-真不敢相信  -在你开口之前
- Fucking believe this. - But before you say anything--
你放走了一个有罪的女人
You let a guilty woman off.
她是无辜的  我知道她是无辜的
She wasn't guilty, and I know it.
你这话听起来和我以前导师说的一样
And that's exactly what my old mentor sounded like
结果他把一个无辜的男人关起来了
when it ended up that he put away a man
而他根本不是杀人凶手
for a murder he didn't commit.
我不是他
Well, I'm not him,
而我也不会为自己做过
and I'm not gonna apologize
必须要做的事情道歉
for doing what I had to.
我根本不在乎你道不道歉
I don't give a shit if you apologize or not.
我们要解决这个问题
We're gonna fix this thing.
你说得对  而我们的解决方式是
You're damn right we are, and we're gonna fix it
暂时吊着贝蒂·帕尔默
by putting Betty Palmer on ice.
贝蒂·帕尔默是哪来的谁
Who the hell is Betty Palmer?
在兰德-考德律所那边被我甩掉的女人
The woman I got rid of from Rand Kaldor
她曾想阻止我做那件事
who tried to stop me from doing what I did.
艾瑞克找到她了
Eric found her.
你知道吗  我不在乎她是谁
You know what? I don't care who she is.
我们要解决这件事
We're gonna fix this,
办法是把你的客户给他们
by you giving them your client.
把一个客户分给那个在背后给罗伯特
There is no way I am giving one of my clients
捅刀子的人  门都没有
to the man who stabbed Robert in the back.
而我也不可能放任你
And there's no way I'm letting you
对一个阻止你犯法的女人
do God-knows-what to a woman
做出来鬼知道什么事
who tried to stop you from breaking the law.
-去你的吧  -够了
- God damn it, you-- - That's enough!
把客户给我  现在就办
Give me your client. Do it now,
否则我保证
or I swear to God,
我会亲手把你掩盖证据的事情上报
I'll hand you in for burying evidence myself.
我想说点什么
I wanted to say something,
和他说我不信任他
to tell him I don't trust him,
和他说我讨厌他
to tell him I hate him--
什么都行
anything.
但我没说
But I didn't.
我就那样...
I just...
坐在那里  接受了
sat there, took it.
路易
Louis,
我想和你尝试做个训练
I'd like to try an exercise with you.
什么训练
What kind of exercise?
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
现在
Now,
想象你正在和查斯走在学校走廊
imagine you are walking down that hallway
走向储物间
with Chaz to the locker.
我不想这样
I don't want to.
相信我
Trust me.
尝试一下
Just try it,
路易
and, Louis,
我要你别把自己想象成
I'd like you to envision yourself
当时年轻的样子
not as a young person,
而是想象成现在的样子
but as you are now.
那么...
So...
告诉我  你看到了什么
tell me what you see.
太可怕了
It's horrible.
我想停下脚步  但我做不到
I want to stop walking, but I can't.
我的腿就那样一直走着
My legs just keep going.
我看见人们看向我
I see people looking.
真是个窝囊废
What a loser.
有人在笑
Some are laughing.
有人压根不在乎
Some don't give a shit.
最糟的是有人在同情我
The worst are the ones who pity me.
我们走到体育室那边
We get to the gym.
空无一人
It's empty.
器械储藏间
我们走向器械储藏间
We walk up to the equipment locker.
他打开门
He opens the door.
我的手停不下来
I can't stop my hand.
我把作业递给了他
I give him his homework.
我不想进那里去
I don't want to go in there,
但我实在没有反抗的勇气了
but I just don't have it in me to fight anymore.
路易  我要你走进储物间
Louis, I need you to go into that locker.
我不想
I don't want to.
我知道
I know.
好吧
Okay.
路易  还有件事
Louis, one more thing.
好吧  现在他和我一起在这里
Okay, he's in here with me now.
很好  现在
Good. Now,
你想对他说什么
what would you like to say to him?
-我不知道  -路易
- I don't know. - Louis--
我跟你说了我不知道
I am telling you, I don't know.
我知道  你和我有过契约
I do. You signed a contract with me,
而你没能履行下去
and you didn't live up to it.
我想履行  但我做不到
I wanted to, but I couldn't.
-为什么  -因为那不只是
- Why not? - Because it's not just
关系到我的个人情感
about my feelings anymore.
那关系到希拉  我们的未来和孩子
It's about Sheila, our future, having a baby.
要是你都没法保护他  要孩子还有什么好处吗
What good is having a baby if you can't protect it?
这么说不公平  要是我对查斯发火
That's not fair. If I lashed out at Chaz,
我会毁掉要孩子的机会  就不能保护他了
I'd ruin our chance at having a child to protect.
瞎扯  那只是借口
Bullshit. That's just an excuse.
你跟查斯什么都没说  是因为你害怕
You didn't say anything to Chaz because you were afraid.
-不是那样的  -你向我保证过的
- That's not true. - You gave me your word.
那只是个蠢孩子的保证
The word of a stupid teenager
他当时还什么都不懂
that didn't understand anything.
-我长大了  -你只不过就是
- I grew up! - You didn't do anything
让他再一次羞辱了我们
except let him humiliate us again,
而且你发誓再也不会如此的
like you swore you would never do.
你说得对
You're right.
没错
I did.
我当时在害怕
I was afraid.
我还在害怕  我永远都会害怕
I'm still afraid. I'll always be afraid.
不  路易  你不会的
No, Louis, you won't.
你不用再害怕查兹了
You don't have to be afraid of Chaz anymore.
为什么
Why not?
因为我刚刚想起你对我们做出的
Because I just remembered another promise
另一个承诺
we made to ourselves,
就是我们单独在这里的时候
when we were all alone in here.
你是说  没有人的时候
You mean, if no one was looking,
我们应该直接...
we should just go ahead and start--
-不是  -不许说我
- Not that one. - Don't judge me.
我们一起在这里待了很久
We were in here a long time.
我是说我们一起待在黑暗中
I mean, we were in here in the dark,
不知道我们还能不能出去的时候
wondering if we'd ever get out.
我们开始哭
We started to cry,
所以我们向自己保证
and we made a promise to ourself
如果有一天
that one day,
如果我们有了孩子
if we ever have children,
我们一定要教那孩子尊重别人
we'd teach our son to treat people with respect,
永远  不要像查兹那样
and to never, ever be like Chaz.
-我都忘了  -我之前也是
- I'd forgotten that. - So did I,
直到你刚才承认你也害怕
until you just admitted you were afraid too.
要是你不介意
If you don't mind,
我希望能打破这个合约
I'd like to break that contract
以兑现那个承诺
so I can keep that promise.
我不介意
I don't mind.
-说好了  -说好了
- So it's a deal? - Deal.
天哪  原来就是这里来的
Jesus. So this is where it comes from.
瞧瞧
Hey, look at that.
门开了
The door's open.
走吧  我们一起出去怎么样
Come on, what do you say we get out of here?
我不知道该说什么  斯坦
I don't know what to say, Stan.
没有你我永远想不起这个承诺
I never would've remembered that promise without you.
我只是帮助你意识到了你的一部分
I just helped you see that a part of you
其实一直还在那个储物间
has always still been in that locker,
而你需要的
and what you needed
就是有个人陪你进去
was someone to be in there with you.
-你是说你吗  -不  路易
- You mean you? - No, Louis.
我是说你
I mean you.
就站那里  我可要好好享受
Stop right there. I want to take this in.
萨曼莎·惠勒  来认输了
Samantha Wheeler, coming in to kiss my ring.
我才不是来认输的
I'm not kissing shit.
我只是来给你这个
I'm coming to give you this.
不认输就滚蛋
My ring or my ass.
我无所谓  反正我赢了
I don't care. I win either way.
不   赢得是贝蒂·帕尔默
No, Betty Palmer wins,
因为她才是
because she's the one
将要接受委托人的人
who's going to represent this client.
再说一遍
You want to try that again?
我说
I said,
委托人是贝蒂的
Betty is the one getting this client,
而我之所以把文件拿来这里
and the only reason I'm bringing their file here
而不是直接给她
instead of to her office
是因为我觉得你给她的文件
is because I don't think the one you gave her
不够多
is big enough
对一个即将成为高级合伙人的人来说
for someone who's about to make senior partner.
我觉得你可能不懂输是什么意思
I don't think you quite get how losing works.
是这样的  输家没有发言权
You see, you don't get to dictate the terms.
我没输  艾瑞克
I didn't lose, Eric.
我只是选择了休战
I chose not to fight anymore,
但我也可以改个主意
but I could change my mind.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你是想消除愧疚感
You're trying to ease your guilt
因为你坑了一个
about screwing over a woman
想做好事的女人
who was trying to do the right thing.
你说的对  是的
You're right. I am.
你根本不知道
And you have no idea
失去这个委托人我损失多惨重
how much losing this client is going to cost me,
但贝蒂知道
but Betty does,
也就是说她会很乐意
which means she'd be more than happy
细细梳理你的文件
to dig through your files
找到我原本的请款单
and find my original billing sheet--
你知道的  能让你被吊销执照的那张
you know, the one that can get you kicked out of the bar.
艾瑞克  你说过
Eric, you said
我把委托人带来这件事就结束
if I brought the client over, this would be over.
你自己没沟通技巧不是我的错
It's not my fault you're a shitty negotiator.
所以让贝蒂当高级合伙人  这事就算完
So make Betty a senior partner and move on,
否则这个公司就要再走一个冠名合伙人了
or this firm is gonna lose another name off its wall,
而这次  那名字是你的
and this time, it'll be yours.
格雷琴  能跟你说两句话吗
Gretchen, can I talk to you for a second?
-我猜猜  -你是对的
- Don't tell me. - You were right.
他们确实要求亚历克斯开除你了
They did demand that Alex fire you.
而他拒绝了
He refused.
不  不行
No. Uh-uh.
我不能接受
I can't let that happen.
什么
What?
我要告诉罗伯特都是我的错
I'm going to tell Robert it was my fault.
我要辞职
I'll retire.
也许这能保住亚历克斯的委托人
Maybe that'll save Alex's client.
格雷琴  这件事不是你的错
Gretchen, what happened was as much my fault as yours.
亚历克斯是对的  我应该追查勒罗伊
Alex was right. I-I should've followed up with Leroy.
那只是个小错误
It was a simple mistake.
而我应该弥补的
And I should've been able to fix it!
我联系了我能找的所有关系
I tried to call in every favor I could.
那女人把我扔出了办公室
That woman laughed me out of the office.
我一直跟我自己说  等我无路可走时
And I always told myself, when I ran out of juice,
我就洗手不干了
I'd hang it up.
我想  我已经走投无路了
Well, turns out, I'm squeezed dry.
格雷琴  我不不知道你该什么时候退休
Gretchen, I can't tell you when it's time,
但我可以告诉你
but I can tell you that it took
是迈克进了监狱才让哈维意识到
Mike going to prison for Harvey
有些错误是没办法弥补的
to learn that some mistakes can't be fixed,
而且我再告诉你一件事
and I'll tell you something else.
迈克离开的那晚
The night that Mike went away,
哈维想过洗手不干
Harvey thought about hanging it up, too,
但如果他真的那么做了  就没办法
but if he tapped out, he couldn't fight
救迈克出来  而内心深处他知道
to get Mike out, and deep down, he knew
他还有战斗的余力
that he still had a lot of fight left in him.
要是我没有了呢
What if I don't?
要是没有我们就不会有这段对话了
You wouldn't be telling me this if you didn't,
因为你提出辞职
because offering to retire
就是一个想弥补这个错误的战斗方式
is just another way of fighting to fix it.
我该怎么面对亚历克斯
How am I supposed to look Alex in the eye tomorrow?
迎面直上
You just do it,
一切都会好的
and it'll be okay,
因为一个愿意为他辞职的人
because someone who would offer to pack it in for him
不是那么多的
doesn't come around very often.
事实上  等他知道的时候
In fact, when he finds out about it,
我打赌他会一大早来我办公室
I bet he is in my office bright and early,
告诉我你该加薪
saying you should get a raise.
你是说你要给我加薪吗
You're saying you're willing to give me a raise?
当然不  你才刚让律所失去了一个委托人
No. You just lost this firm a huge client.
谢谢  红毛
Thanks, Red.
我希望哪天你考虑
I hope that when you're thinking
放弃时
about packing it in,
你也能有个
you have someone like you
像你一样的人说服你不要放弃
to talk you out of it too.
格雷琴
Gretchen
抱一个
get yourself on over here.
好了吗
Is it done?
好了
It's done.
不论如何
For what it's worth,
我们合作地不错
we threw some good punches.
我怎么没这种感觉呢
Just doesn't feel that way.
也许那是好事
Well, maybe that's a good thing.
为什么
How's that?
因为下次卡尔多再来
Because the next time Kaldor comes around,
你会想起这种感觉
you're gonna remember how this felt.
你说我们一起去健身房
What do you say we hit the gym
过两招怎么样
and go a few rounds?
-今晚算了  -为什么
- Not tonight. - Why not?
我会不开心
Because I'd feel bad
因为我丢了委托人  还要让你赢
that I'd lost a client, and I'd let you win,
而我不想让着你
and I don't want to let you win.
你是真觉得自己能赢我是吗
You really think you can beat me, don't you?
我知道我能赢
I know I can.
你面对艾瑞克·卡尔多好像也是这么想的
Isn't that what you thought about Eric Kaldor?
那不一样  你很清楚
That's different, and you know it.
我跟你说清楚  萨曼莎
Let me tell you something, Samantha.
我从来没想过我会输
I never thought I could lose
直到迈克进了监狱
until Mike Ross went to prison.
我现在依然觉得我不会输
I still don't ever think I'm gonna lose,
但是
but...
我心里知道  我输过一次的
I know in the back of my mind that one time I did.
只是我的想法
It's just a thought.
我会记住的
I'll keep that in mind.
晚安  哈维
Good night, Harvey.
晚安  萨曼莎
Good night, Samantha.
哈维
Harvey?
只是想说
Just so you know,
如果下次我还能让无辜的人避免入狱
if I had another chance to keep an innocent woman
我还会那么做的
out of prison, I'd do it again.
那是你和你的信念的事了
That's between you and your maker,
但如果还有下次
but if there is a next time,
确保没有贝蒂·帕尔默这个人物好吗
how about you make sure there aren't any Betty Palmers?